

SAI SURAJ MOHANTY

Regional College of Management



saisuraj386@gmail.com



+91-7978058836

12990b108



linkedin.com/in/sai-suraj-mohanty-

Dhamilo, Kothapatna, Odisha,754001

in

nt skills looking forward an opportunity in

A hardworking, smart and persuasive individual with time management skills looking forward an opportunity in marketing industry to prove my skills. A person with excellent knowledge in social media marketing and lean six sigma desiring to contribute towards the benefit of the company by anticipating market shifts and also possess an additional experience of Research analysis.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SUMMER INTERNSHIP

Indian Aviation Industry

06/2020 - 08/2020

Bhubaneswar, India

Indian aviation industry is the fastest growing aviation market and the 5th largest market in terms of Aircraft passengers Achievements / Tasks

- Research Analyst: Predicted and analyzed the effect of COVID-19 pandemic upon Indian aviation sector.
- Estimating consumer demand and measuring aviation industry growth on COVID-19 Pandemic.

LUM Events

08/2020 - 09/2020

Bhubaneswar, India

LUM Event Pvt Ltd organises and hosts private party, wedding party, promotion management events etc. in a suitable price.

Achievements / Tasks

- Research Intern: Analysis on different venues, artists, catering group, fashion designers for being associated with LUM Events.

LIVE PROJECT

Parle Products Pvt Ltd

12/2019 – 01/2020

Bhubaneswar, India

Parle Pvt Ltd.is an Indian food product company. It owns the famous biscuit brand Parle-G.

Achievements / Tasks

- Research Analyst: predicted and analyzed the growth and demand of Parle products (Hide&Seek) for the year 2020-21.
- Suggestion for better supply chain management in both urban and rural area.

EDUCATION

Post-Graduate Diploma in Management (Marketing, Operation)

Pursuing (2019-2021)

Regional college of Management, Bhubaneswar

Bachelor of Science | 67.22 % (2015-2018)

Sri Jayadev (degree) college of education and technology, Naharakanta, Bhubaneswar

Intermediate in Science | 59 % (2013-2015)

Brahmanjharilo Mahavidyalaya, Cuttack

Matriculation | 69% (2013) Radhamadhab Bidyapitha, Cuttack

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- M.S Office Package
- Operating system.
- Digital marketing (Google digital unlocked)
- Content Marketing

SOFT SKILLS

Interpersonal skills

- Leadership skills
- Persuasive skills

Time management

- Prioritizing time line
- Focusing and achieving goals

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Participated in the e-start Up boot camp (an Initiative by start-up Odisha) held in RCM on 2019.
- Participated in the 2nd annual leadership summit 2019 conducted at Swosti Premium, Bhubaneswar.
- Participated a 3 -Days campus preparatory workshop (AMA) by LinkedIn local Bhubaneswar.

AVOCATION

- Gardening
- Playing Badminton & Cricket
- Surfing the Internet

CERTIFICATES

- Lean Six Sigma White Belt Certification from Management of Strategy Institute, Philadelphia.

Design thinking certification from CHRD,

Bhubaneswar.

 Certification on Strategic framework of Marketing.